const quizData = [
  {
    subject: "Mathematics",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Find the sum of 111 + 222 + 333",
        options: [700, 666, 10, 100],
        correctOption: 666,
      },
      {
        question: "Subtract 357 from 932",
        options: [10, 68, 575, 765],
        correctOption: 575,
      },
      {
        question: " 70 times 5 is equal to",
        options: [350, 686, 12, 705],
        correctOption: 350,
      },
      {
        question: "Simplify: 26 + 182 - 12",
        options: [70, 196, 190, 140],
        correctOption: 196,
      },
      {
        question: " Solve : 24 + 4 รท 4",
        options: [25, 6, 28, 10],
        correctOption: 25,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    subject: "Coding",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What is Html?",
        options: [
          "Hypertext Markup Language",
          "Hypotext Markup Language",
          "Hypertext Makeup Language",

          "Hypertext Mockup Language",
        ],
        correctOption: "Hypertext Markup Language",
      },
      {
        question: "Is CSS a programming Language",
        options: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "I don't know"],
        correctOption: "No",
      },
      {
        question: "Javascript is the same as Java",
        options: ["True", "False", "Maybe", "I don't know"],
        correctOption: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Javascript can only be used for Web development",
        options: ["True", "False", "Maybe", "I don't know"],
        correctOption: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "What is '2' + '2'",
        options: [4, 22, 5, 10],
        correctOption: 22,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    subject: "English",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What is correct?",
        options: [
          "Circumstance",
          "Circummstance",
          "Circcumstance",

          "Circumstanse",
        ],
        correctOption: "Circumstance",
      },
      {
        question: "Which is wrong?",
        options: ["Communicate", "Circumstance", "Counterfeit", "Contantment"],
        correctOption: "Contantment",
      },
      {
        question: "Which is a noun?",
        options: ["Advice", "Advise", "Coming", "feeling"],
        correctOption: "Advice",
      },
      {
        question: "Which is odd?",
        options: ["Country", "City", "Town", "People"],
        correctOption: "People",
      },
      {
        question: "What is odd?",
        options: ["Apple", "Orange", "Green", "Red"],
        correctOption: "Apple",
      },
    ],
  },
];
